[
    {
        "question": "What update does the KSampler node now support in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "The KSampler node in ComfyUI now supports a preview function, which requires the installation of ComfyUI-Manager to utilize."
    },
    {
        "question": "What must be done to enable the preview function for the KSampler node?",
        "answer": "To enable the preview function for the KSampler node, you must first install ComfyUI-Manager."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the startup settings support in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "The startup settings in ComfyUI support disabling the Python Checking feature, which speeds up the application launch when turned off, and also support manual entry of additional ComfyUI startup commands."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which issues were resolved with the Reroute and Primitive nodes in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "In ComfyUI, the issues with the Reroute node where it could not be used and the problem with the Primitive node being inoperable were resolved."
    },
    {
        "question": "What fixes were made regarding WebSocket and workflow in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "ComfyUI addressed the WebSocket disconnection issue and corrected the workflow running pause issue, where the status remained as running."
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the HDR Effects plugin offer in ComfyUI?",
        "answer": "The HDR Effects plugin in ComfyUI offers an image processing application that enhances the dynamic range and visual appeal of input images, providing adjustable parameters for users to fine-tune the HDR effect."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the key features of the ComfyUI_ColorMod plugin?",
        "answer": "ComfyUI_ColorMod can adjust brightness/contrast, edit hues, and supports HDR images. It also has the capability to save images as 16-bit PNG files."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a unique capability of the human-parser-comfyui-node plugin?",
        "answer": "The human-parser-comfyui-node plugin can automatically extract masks for body regions and clothing/fashion items, such as upper clothes, left arm, and right arm in images."
    },
    {
        "question": "What can GRM do in terms of 3D reconstruction?",
        "answer": "GRM, a large Gaussian Reconstruction Model, can reconstruct accurate 3D models in a short time by efficiently integrating multi-view information and supports converting text or images directly into 3D models."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the goal of the Polaris LLM system?",
        "answer": "The goal of the Polaris LLM system, developed by Hippocratic AI, is to create an AI system capable of safely and effectively engaging in long, multi-turn voice conversations with patients, providing professional and accurate medical advice."
    }
]